Finding Aid for Detroit Urban League 1916-1992
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Detroit Urban League records 1916-1992
Detroit Urban League.
851100 Bd 2 UBDm
Social Service organization serving the Detroit African American community, affiliate of the National Urban League; includes minutes of the Board of Directors, correspondence and topical files of Executive Directors and Presidents, budgets and financial records, and papers concerning National Urban League conferences and Green Pastures Camp; also departmental files relating to community services, housing, vocational services, health and welfare, job development and employment, and education and youth incentives; and photographs.
96 linear feet
1 oversize folders
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection (Donor No. 4042 ) has been received in several accessions beginning in 1963. Periodic additions to the collection continue.
The collection is open for research except for boxes 35-36.
The 16mm films in the collection were digitized in 2009 as part of a library video preservation project. Preservation master beta tapes for all titles and high resolution digital files of some titles were created along with DVD and streaming files for all titles. The DVDs are available for use in the library. A selection of the streaming files may be available online at a given time, others can be mounted on request.
The Detroit Urban League (hereafter referred to as the D.U.L.), an affiliate of the National Urban League (N.U.L.), was founded in 1916 to address the needs of the growing population of African-Americans in Detroit. The N.U.L. had been founded in 1910 in New York as the National League on Urban Conditions Among Negroes as an agency responsive to the needs of Black emigrants from the south who were then coming in great numbers to the urban north.
The establishment of the D.U.L. was a joint effort of the N.U.L. and the Associated Charities of Detroit. The D.U.L. was and is a problem oriented agency, creating programs and services to meet the most pressing educational, employment, health, and social needs of the Detroit African American community.
The D.U.L. was at first funded by the Associated Charities of Detroit (which later evolved into the Community Fund). It has also, in the past, received allocations from the N.U.L. In 1992, the D.U.L. received funding from the Community Fund's successor United Community Services of Detroit, the local United Way Foundation; from local, federal and state grants; and from N.U.L. grants and individual D.U.L. memberships.
The D.U.L., although it operates as an independent agency, is linked to the national organization through the N.U.L.'s "Terms of Affiliation." Policy is set by a board of directors and a strong executive director/president. The D.U.L. chief executive officers since its founding have been:
1916-1918 Forrester B. Washington, Executive Director
1918-1960 John C. Dancy, Executive Director
1960-1978 Francis A. Kornegay, Executive Director
1978-1984 Roy Levy Williams, President
1984-1985 Sue Hamilton-Smith, Interim President
1985-1987 Donald W. Woods, President
1987- N. Charles Anderson, President
For further information on the D.U.L. records, the researcher should consult
A Brief History of the Detroit Urban League and Description of the League's Papers in the Michigan Historical Collections (Michigan Historical Collections Bulletin No. 20)
and the MHC's
Guide to the Microfilm Edition of the Detroit Urban League Papers.
These bulletins also contain references to other sources of information about the D.U.L. at the Michigan Historical Collections and elsewhere. The researcher should additionally consult the papers of John C. Dancy and Francis A. Kornegay and the records of the Children's Fund of Michigan also located at the Michigan Historical Collections. For a perspective on the D.U.L.'s Green Pastures Camp,
Keri Bancroft's "Green Pastures Camp: Scene II" (Michigan History Magazine, 69, no. 5, September/October 1985, pp. 32-39)
is a useful source.
A separate collection of D.U.L. materials is located at the Burton Historical Collections of the Detroit Public Library; while the records of United Community Services of Detroit are at the Wayne State University Labor Archives.
The records of the Detroit Urban League have been received in a series of accessions beginning in 1963. The first four accessions, 1963-1971, were reprocessed in 1977 and have been designated "Original Accessions." Beginning in 1977, upon receipt of new materials, the decision was made to process subsequent accessions as separate units of the collection, even though they might contain materials from an earlier period. These later groupings of files are labeled "1977 Accession. Records, 1936-1977," "1985 Accession. Records, 1939-1985," and "1992 Accession. Records, 1924-1992." The four accessions with their principal series are:
Original Accessions, 1916-1963 (Boxes 1-56)
Executive Director's Files
General Files and Correspondence
Topical Files
Board of Directors
National Urban League Conferences
Budget and Financial Records
Printed Materials
Green Pastures Camp
Detroit House of Corrections
Social Welfare Cases [CLOSED]
Departmental Files
Community Services Department
Vocational Services Department
Housing Department
Educational and Youth Incentives Department
Health and Welfare Department
Job Development and Employment Department
1977 Accession, 1936-1977 (Boxes 57-73)
National Urban League Files
National Conferences
Memos
Press Releases
Office Files
Subject File
National Council on Social Work
Publications
Urban League Affiliates
Detroit Urban League Files
Executive Board Materials
Departmental Reports
Research Reports
Correspondence
Memos
Speech File
Publications
Reference File
Green Pastures File
Audio tapes
1985 Accession, 1939-1985 (Boxes 74-87)
Executive Director's Files
John C. Dancy, 1926-1967
Francis A. Kornegay, 1951-1978
President's Files
Roy L. Williams, 1978-1985
Photographs
Films
1992 Accession, 1924-1992 (Boxes 88-96)
Executive Director's Files
Francis A. Kornegay, 1960-1978
President's Files
Roy Levy Williams,1978-1984
Sue Hamilton-Smith, 1984-84
Donald Woods, 1985-19897
N. Charles Anderson, 1987 -
Deputy Director's Files, 1968-1978
Staff Files, 1974-1989
The records of the Detroit Urban League include minutes of the Board of Directors, correspondence and topical files of Executive Directors and Presidents, budgets and financial records, and papers concerning National Urban League conferences and Green Pastures Camp; also departmental files relating to community services, housing, vocational services, health and welfare, job development and employment, and education and youth incentives. The records also include photographs of chapter activities, meetings, and ceremonies; photos of buildings and staff (notably executive directors, John Dancy and Francis Kornegay); also films.
Subjects:
Afro-Americans--Michigan.; Anderson, N. Charles.; Camps--Michigan.; Charities--Michigan--Detroit.; Civil rights--Michigan--Detroit.; Depressions--1929--Michigan--Detroit.; Detroit (Mich.); Detroit (Mich.). House of Correction.; Detroit (Mich.). Housing Commission.; Detroit (Mich.). Commission on Children and Youth.; Detroit (Mich.). Commission on Community Relations.; Detroit Federation of Settlements.; Detroit Urban League.; Education--Michigan--Detroit.; Hamilton-Smith, Sue.; Housing--Michigan.; Labor--Michigan--Detroit.; Michigan Welfare League.; Municipal government--Michigan--Detroit.; National Urban League.; New Deal, 1933-1939--Michigan--Detroit.; Social service--Michigan--Detroit--Societies, etc.; Unemployed--Michigan--Detroit.; Williams, Roy L.; Woods, Donald W.; Youth--Michigan--Detroit.; Green Pastures Camp (Mich.)
Visual Materials - Subjects
Afro-Americans--Health and welfare.; Afro-Americans--Organizations.; Buildings--Michigan--Detroit.; Green Pastures Camp (Mich.); Camps.; Central Methodist Church (Detroit, Mich.); Charitable organizations.; Children.; Churches--Michigan--Detroit.; Dancy, John C. (John Campbell), 1888-1968.; Detroit (Mich.)--Buildings.; Detroit (Mich.)--Churches.; Detroit Urban League.; Kornegay, Francis A.; Nursing--Michigan--Detroit.; Offices.
Sound Recordings - Subjects
Detroit Urban League.; Afro-Americans--Michigan--Detroit.; Detroit (Mich.); Sound recordings.; Kornegay, Francis A.
Contributors:
Dancy, John C. (John Campbell), 1888-1968.; Kornegay, Francis A.; Washington, Forrester B.
Genre/Form:
Photographs.; Motion pictures.
- Original Accession
  (The bulk of this accessions is available on microfilm.)
  - Executive Director's Files
    Executive Directors' Files, 1916-1969 (boxes 1-36) include the general correspondence and topical files of Forrester B. Washington and John Dancy; minutes of meetings of the League's Board of Directors; budget and financial records; files concerning National Urban League. conferences and the Green Pastures Camp program. The series also includes printed pamphlets, reports, newsletters and books produced by for the Detroit Urban League and other Urban League chapters.
    - General Files and Correspondence
      - undated June 1916-February 1930 (Box 1)
        [1-1, etc. - 1-32]
      - March 1930-December 1933 (Box 2)
        [2-1, etc. - 2-36]
      - January 1934-May 1937 (Box 3)
        [3-1, etc. - 3-35]
      - June 1937-February 1943 (Box 4)
        [4-1, etc. - 4-35]
      - March 1943-December 1949 (Box 5)
        [5-1, etc. - 5-31]
      - 1950-1960 (Box 6)
        [6-1, etc. - 6-27]
    - Topical Files 1918-1960
      - American Association of Social Workers 1932-1954 (Box 6)
        [6-28, 6-29]
      - American Red Cross 1942-1954 (Box 6)
        [6-30]
      - American War -- Community Service 1944 (Box 6)
        [6-31]
      - Baby Clinic 1921-1926 (Box 6)
        [6-32]
      - Bethune-Cookman Emergency Campaign 1933 (Box 6)
        [6-33]
      - Bibliographies (Box 7)
        [7-2, 7-2]
      - Brochure on Human Relations 1952 (Box 7)
        [7-3]
      - Charities Registration Bureau of Detroit 1930-1932 (Box 7)
        [7-4]
      - Community Fund Campaign 1926, 1929-1949 (Box 7)
        [7-5, etc. - 7-24]
      - Council of Social Agencies undated, 1944-1951 (Box 7)
        [7-25, etc. - 7-31]
      - Department Directors Meetings 1956-1959 (Box 7)
        [7-32]
      - Detroit Commission on Community Relations 1953-1959 (Box 8)
        [8-1, etc. - 8-10]
      - Detroit Council for Youth Services 1935-1951 (Box 8)
        [8-11, etc. - 8-13]
      - Detroit Council of Social Workers 1928-1938 (Box 8)
        [8-14]
      - Detroit Counseling Service 1946-1951 (Box 8)
        [8-15]
      - Detroit Department of Public Welfare 1933-1934 (Box 8)
        [8-16]
      - Detroit Federation of Settlements 1922-1954 (Box 8)
        [8-17a, etc. - 8-27]
      - Detroit House of Correction 1943-1946 (Box 8)
        [8-28]
      - Detroit Urban League Associates 1943 (Box 8)
        [8-29]
      - Detroit Urban League Community Center 1918-1925 (Box 8)
        [8-30, 8-31]
      - Employers' Association of Detroit 1920-1928 (Box 9)
        [9-1, etc. - 9-5]
      - Film Script 1955 (Box 9)
        [9-6]
      - Governor's Insurance Study 1949-1950 (Box 9)
        [9-7]
      - Job Placement Reports 1924-1925 (Box 9)
        [9-8, 9-9]
      - McCoy Orphanage 1909-1915 (Box 9)
        [9-10]
      - Mayor's Unemployment Committee 1930-1933 (Box 9)
        [9-11, 9-13]
      - Michigan People's Finance Corporation 1928-1938 (Box 9)
        [9-13, etc. - 9-15]
      - National Dental Association Convention 1947 (Box 9)
        [9-16]
      - National Industrial Conference Board 1929-1938 (Box 9)
        [9-17]
      - National Medical Association Convention 1949 (Box 9)
        [9-18]
      - National Urban League
        - Executive Secretaries Council 1943-1948 (Box 9)
          [9-19]
        - Fellowships 1935 (Box 9)
          [9-20]
        - Merit Rating Plan 1947-1948 (Box 9)
          [9-21]
        - Reports on Industry 1926-1927 (Box 9)
          [9-22]
      - Non-profit Corporation Reports 1924-1946 (Box 9)
        [9-23]
      - Parkside Hospital 1933-1955 (Box 9)
        [9-24, etc. - 9-37]
      - Pen and Palette Club 1926-1931 (Box 10)
        [10-1, 10-2]
      - Press Releases 1951-1956 (Box 10)
        [10-3]
      - Public Relations 1951-1955 (Box 10)
        [10-4]
      - Russian War Relief 1942-1946 (Box 10)
        [10-5]
      - Selective Service 1940-1942 (Box 10)
        [10-6]
      - Social Workers Club of Detroit 1930-1938 (Box 10)
        [10-7]
      - Speech Material (Box 10)
        10-8, 10-9, 10-10]
      - Staff Meetings 1956-1960 (Box 10)
        [10-11, 10-12]
      - Stay at Home Camp 1949 (Box 10)
        [10-13]
      - Survey of Black Policemen 1923 (Box 10)
        [10-14]
      - Tuskegee Fund Drive 1925-1926 (Box 10)
        [10-15]
      - United Community Services 1951-1954 (Box 10)
        [10-16, etc. - 10-23]
      - United Negro College Fund 1951-1958 (Box 10)
        [10-24]
      - USO of Metropolitan Detroit 1951 (Box 10)
        [10-25]
      - U.S. Department of Labor Group Work Reports 1936-1938 (Box 10)
        [10-26, 10-27]
      - Work Reports
        - 1921 (Box 10)
          [10-28]
        - 1926-1935 (Box 10)
          [10-29, etc. - 10-38]
      - Y.M.C.A. 1926-1932 (Box 10)
        [10-39]
    - Board of Directors
      - Minutes and Reports
        - 1916-1938 (Box 11)
          [11-0, etc. - 11-14]
        - 1940-1945 (Box 11)
          [11-15]
        - 1950-1968 (Box 11)
          [11-16, etc. - 11-27]
      - General File
        - 1945-1954 (Box 11)
          [11-28, etc. - 11-32]
        - 1955-1969 (Box 12)
          [12-1, etc. - 12-20]
    - National Urban League Conferences
      - 1937-1941 (Box 12)
        [12-21, etc. - 12-27]
      - 1944 (Box 12)
        [12-28]
      - 1947 (Box 12)
        [12-29]
      - 1948-1958 (Box 13)
        [13-1, etc. - 13-28]
      - 1958-1964 (Box 14)
        [14-1, etc. - 14-19]
      - 1967 (Box 14)
        [14-20]
    - Budgets and Financial Records
      - 1916-1932 (Box 14)
        [14-21, etc. - 14-30]
      - 1933-1946 (Box 15)
        [15-1, etc. - 15-30]
      - 1947-1955 (Box 16)
        [16-1, etc. - 16-26]
      - 1956-1962 (Box 17)
        [17-1, etc. - 17-28]
      - 1963-1968 (Box 18)
        [18-1, etc. - 18-11]
    - Printed Material
      - Detroit Urban League Printed Material
        - 1951-1969 (Box 18)
          [18-14, etc. - 18-19]
      - National Urban League Printed Material
        - undated 1916-1948 (Box 18)
          [18-20, etc. - 18-27]
        - 1949-1966 (Box 19)
          [19-1, etc. - 19-17]
        - 1968 (Box 19)
          [19-18]
      - Administrative and Clerical Council Jottings
        - 1957-1958 (Box 19)
          [19-19, 19-20, 19-21]
        - 1960-1961 (Box 19)
          [19-22, 19-23, 19-24]
      - Printed Materials of Urban League Affiliates
        - Baltimore 1947-1953 (Box 19)
          [19-25]
        - Brooklyn 1919-1932 (Box 19)
          [19-26]
        - Chicago 1918-1959 (Box 19)
          [19-27, 19-28]
        - Dayton 1952-1956 (Box 19)
          [19-29]
        - Kansas City 1927-1935 (Box 19)
          [19-30]
        - Los Angeles 1948-1961 (Box 19)
          [19-31]
        - Milwaukee 1929-1958 (Box 19)
          [19-32]
      - Printed Materials of Urban League Affiliates
        - New York 1919-1963 (Box 20)
          [20-1]
        - Omaha 1929-1966 (Box 20)
          [20-2]
        - Pittsburgh
          - 1927-1935 (Box 20)
            [20-3]
          - 1950-1959 (Box 20)
            [20-4]
        - St. Louis 1926-1959 (Box 20)
          [20-5]
        - St. Paul 1930-1952 (Box 20)
          [20-6]
        - Seattle 1931-1958 (Box 20)
          [20-7]
        - Washington 1956-1961 (Box 20)
          [20-8]
        - Miscellaneous 1916-1964 (Box 20)
          [20-9, etc. - 20-16]
      - Michigan and Detroit Printed Materials
        - undated 1920-1942 (Box 20)
          [20-17, etc. - 20-33]
        - 1943-1957 (Box 21)
          [21-1, etc. - 21-30]
        - 1958-1969 (Box 22)
          [22-1, etc. - 22-22]
      - Miscellaneous Printed Materials
        - undated 1918-1929 (Box 22)
          [22-23, etc. - 22-27]
        - 1930-1958 (Box 23)
          [23-1, etc. - 23-31]
        - 1959-1970 (Box 24)
          [24-1, etc. - 24-15]
      - Books
        - Report of the Mumford High School Study Committee 1967 (Box 24)
        - Children and Youth in Michigan 1960 (Box 24)
        - Substandard Regional Speech in a Northern Industrial Area 1956 (Box 24)
        - Administrative Survey of the Wayne County General Hospital 1954 (Box 24)
      - Newspaper Clippings
        - undated 1917-1970 (Box 25)
          [25-1, etc. - 25-26]
    - Green Pastures Camp
      - Annual Reports
        - 1931-1947 (Box 25)
          [25-27, etc. - 25-30]
        - 1948-1954 (Box 26)
          [26-1, etc. - 26-6]
        - 1958 (Box 26)
          [26-7]
      - General File
        - 1931-1962 (Box 26)
          [26-8, etc. - 26-27]
        - 1963-1965 (Box 27)
          [27-1, 27-2, 27-3]
      - Budgets and Financial Records
        - 1931-1935 (Box 27)
          [27-4, etc. - 27-9]
        - 1937-1941 (Box 27)
          [27-10]
        - 1943-1955 (Box 27)
          [27-11, etc. - 27-32]
        - 1956-1963 (Box 28)
          [28-1, etc. - 28-25]
        - 1964-1965 (Box 29)
          [29-1, 29-2, 29-3]
      - Applications
        - 1931-1949 (Box 29)
          [29-1, etc. - 29-29]
        - 1953-1955 (Box 29)
          [29-30, etc. - 29-33]
        - 1956-1962 (Box 30)
          [30-1, etc. - 30-23]
      - 1962-1965 (Box 31)
        [31-1, etc. - 31-21]
      - Camp Study Committee
        - 1956-1958 (Box 31)
          [31-22, 31-23]
      - Alfred Camp
        - 1941-1942 (Box 31)
          [31-24]
    - Urban League Job Applications and Recommendations
      - 1925-1954 (Box 32)
        [32-1, etc. - 32-25]
      - 1955-1968 (Box 33)
        [33-1, etc. - 33-6]
    - Detroit House of Correction
      - Weekly Reports
        - January 1933-February 1936 (Box 33)
          [33-7, etc. - 33-25]
        - March 1936-September 1937 (Box 34)
          [34-1, etc. - 34-8]
        - 1939-1940 (Box 34)
          [34-9]
        - 1943-1944 (Box 34)
          [34-10, etc. - 34-13]
    - Sand Against the Wind
      - (Manuscript of book) (Box 34)
        [34-14, etc. - 34-18]
    - Detroit Urban League Guild
      - Account Book 1961-1965 (Box 34)
    - Social Welfare Cases
      [CLOSED] January 1, 2018
      - undated 1916-1933 (Box 35)
        [35-1, etc. - 35-10]
      - 1935-1938 (Box 35)
        [35-11, etc. - 35-14]
      - 1942-1945 (Box 35)
        [35-15, 35-16]
      - 1950-1962 (Box 35)
        [35-17, etc. - 35-27]
      - 1964-1969 (Box 35)
        [35-28, etc. - 35-31]
      - 1920-1930, 2 folders (Box 35)
        [1977 accession]
      - 1916-1933, 17 folders (Box 36)
  - Departmental Files
    The Departmental Files series, 1947-1968 (boxes 37-56) consists of the records of the Community Services and Vocational Services Departments from the early 1940s to 1963 and the records of the Housing Department, the Education and Youth Incentives Department, the Health and Welfare Department, and the Job Development and Employment Department from 1964 through 1968.
    - Community Service Department
      - Reports 1947-1963, 13 folders (Box 37)
      - General File
        - Undated, 7 folders (Box 37)
        - January 1947-June 1950, 8 folders (Box 37)
        - July 1950-April 1957 (Box 38)
          24 folders
        - May 1957-May 1962, 26 folders (Box 39)
        - June 1962-December 1963, 8 folders (Box 40)
      - Topical File
        - Adoption Clearance Committee 1958-1963, 2 folders (Box 40)
        - Adoptions 1953-1959 (Box 40)
        - Aging 1958-1960, 2 folders (Box 40)
        - Aid to Dependent Children 1962 (Box 40)
        - Anti-Defamation League 1957-1963, 2 folders (Box 40)
        - Block Clubs 1962 (Box 40)
        - Brewster and Jeffries Projects 1952-1955, 2 folders (Box 40)
        - Brochure on Housing Mobility 1955 (Box 40)
        - Cherrylawn and Chippewa Dads' Club 1955 (Box 40)
        - Child Welfare Advisory Committee 1957-1963, 5 folders (Box 40)
        - Child Welfare Institute 1957, 2 folders (Box 40)
        - Citizens' Advisory Committee on Police Procedures 1960 (Box 41)
        - Citizens' Advisory Committee on School Needs 1957-1960 (Box 41)
        - Citizens' Committee to Combat Crime 1959-1960, 2 folders (Box 41)
        - Civil Rights Hearings 1960, 2 folders (Box 41)
        - Community Services and Urban Living 1959 (Box 41)
        - Coordinating Council on Civil Rights 1961 (Box 41)
        - Crime Institute 1960 (Box 41)
        - Delta Home for Girls 1953-1956 (Box 41)
        - Detroit Commission on Children and Youth 1959-1963, 4 folders (Box 41)
        - Detroit Committee for Neighborhood Preservation and Improved Housing
          - 1953-1957, 3 folders (Box 41)
          - 1960-1963, 3 folders (Box 41)
        - Detroit Council of Churches 1956-1957 (Box 41)
        - Detroit Federation of Community Councils 1962-1963 (Box 41)
        - Detroit Housing Commission
          - 1949-1953, 7 folders (Box 41)
          - 1954-1955, 4 folders (Box 42)
          - 1957-1963, 4 folders (Box 42)
        - Detroit Public Schools 1949-1956, 2 folders (Box 42)
        - Discriminatory Practices in Social Welfare Agencies 1959 (Box 42)
        - East Side Planning Commission 1962 (Box 42)
        - Eight Mile - Wyoming Project 1962-1963 (Box 42)
        - Equal Opportunity Day 1962 (Box 42)
        - Federal Housing Administration
          - 1950-1952 (Box 42)
          - 1962-1963 (Box 42)
        - Field Contacts 1959 (Box 42)
        - Financing of Home Purchases 1954-1963, 2 folders (Box 42)
        - Greater Detroit Committee for Fair Housing Practices 1961-1963 (Box 42)
        - Higher Education - Financial Assistance 1963 (Box 42)
        - Hospital and Medical Center Studies
          - Undated (Box 42)
          - 1951-1956, 7 folders (Box 42)
          - 1957-1962, 4 folders (Box 43)
        - Housing
          - 1947-1950, 2 folders (Box 43)
          - 1963 (Box 43)
        - Housing and Home Finance Agency 1951-1956 (Box 43)
        - Housing Legislation 1957-1963 (Box 43)
        - Housing Needs of Older People 1953-1957 (Box 43)
        - Housing Research Material 1957-1960 (Box 43)
        - Housing Survey 1952 (Box 43)
        - Improvement Associations 1955-1957 (Box 43)
        - Institute for Neighborhood Leaders
          - 1954 (Box 43)
          - 1956 (Box 43)
        - Institutes and Forums 1954-1958 (Box 43)
        - Institutional Needs of Negro Delinquent Boys 1957-1959 (Box 43)
        - Integration of Public Housing 1957 (Box 43)
        - Job Descriptions 1957-1960 (Box 43)
        - Manual Revision Committee 1951-1959, 2 folders (Box 43)
        - Mayor's Committee on Children and Youth 1954 (Box 43)
        - Memorandums 1956-1963, 3 folders (Box 43)
        - Michigan Welfare League 1961-1963, 4 folders (Box 43)
        - National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials 1962 (Box 43)
        - Neighborhood Activity 1955 (Box 43)
        - Neighborhood Changes 1961-1962, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Neighborhood Organizations 1954 (Box 44)
        - Newburgh Plan 1961 (Box 44)
        - Newspaper Clippings 1961-1963 (Box 44)
        - North Woodward Community Council 1952-1956 (Box 44)
        - Northwest Branch 1947-1954, 5 folders (Box 44)
        - Parents' Institute 1960, 2 folders (Box 44)
        - Plaintiff's Brief - Ming vs. Horgan 1958 (Box 44)
        - Police Community Relations 1963 (Box 44)
        - Population Figures (Box 44)
        - Real Estate Brokers' Committee 1961 (Box 44)
        - Rental Housing Project (Box 44)
        - Speeches 1962-1963 (Box 44)